<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Academic</title>
    <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 post</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/7/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Most Popular Programming Languages</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1java-language&#34;&gt;1.Java language&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A general-purpose programming language that consistently ranks high in popularity ratings. Java applications can run on any computer; a Java virtual machine has been created for this. Java is actively developing mobile applications for the Android operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Such successful projects as RuneScape, Yahoo, Amazon, eBay, LinkedIn are written in Java.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The disadvantages of Java are the slow operation of programs and the high consumption of RAM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2c-language&#34;&gt;2.C language&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The C language is used to develop operating systems and real-time applications. It is also used as an intermediate when compiling higher-level languages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The C language is complex and contains elements that can easily be mistaken, it contributes to the creation of confusing and far from safe code. For 40 years of existence, it has become obsolete, and this significantly reduces its performance in our time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The C syntax became the basis for other programming languages: C++, Java, C# and Objective-C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;3javascript-language&#34;&gt;3.JavaScript language&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not confuse it with Java - they are different and completely different languages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JavaScript is used to create graphics, mobile and web applications, in browser operating systems. It is very versatile and quite easy to learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;4php-language&#34;&gt;4.PHP language&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Widely used to create web applications, leading in use for creating dynamic sites. PHP has gone through a rapid evolution and has become in demand among programmers. However, it is often criticized by programmers for its inconsistent syntax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;5python-language&#34;&gt;5.Python language&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python is easy to learn and is very often used when teaching children to code - for example, in Skysmart online school. Programs in Python are close to natural language, so it is great as a first language for a novice programmer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a very common language, a large number of projects have been implemented in it. Python is heavily used by Google, and most of YouTube&amp;rsquo;s source code is written in it. It is also often used in the creation of robotic machines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strengths of Python are modularity and the ability to integrate with other languages, and among the disadvantages are low speed and high memory consumption.
S&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 post</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instruction</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;14-tips-for-making-a-presentation-youre-not-ashamed-of&#34;&gt;14 tips for making a presentation you&amp;rsquo;re not ashamed of&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good presentation starts with questions to yourself. You can do the most important part in notepad without even turning on your computer. First, you choose a topic, define a goal, distribute the arguments in the right order. And only now you can open the program and look for pictures for the presentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formulate a topic
It is difficult to listen to an interlocutor who jumps from one to another, so the presentation should have only one topic. Otherwise, it will be a long story about nothing. The topic should be narrow enough to offer a solution to the problem at the end. Narrow the topic down until the presentation can be summed up in ten short paragraphs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Determining a good topic is easy - it itself suggests the structure of the speech.
Broad topic, thought jumps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define a goal
A good presentation changes the existing picture of the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good presentation goal starts with the question: what do I want to change in the behavior of the listeners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think of a script
The purpose of the presentation is what you want to change in the listener&amp;rsquo;s head, and the script is how you will arrive at those changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show examples
Less theory, more life. Show how your product works and how people use it. See how they do it on Kickstarter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alternate slides
Presentation is like text. If the text consists of sentences of the same length and the same type, it will be boring to read. There is no rhythm. Therefore, alternate text slides and slides with images, add graphics. Sometimes you can joke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lyrics are shorter
One slide, one thought. This slide is easy to read and remember. If you are speaking in public, he will keep the attention of the audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 post</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIT</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;git&#34;&gt;git&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GIT is one such system. GIT uses a distributed model instead of the traditional client-server model. Thus, GIT repositories do not need a centralized repository: the entire history of document changes is stored on each computer, in local storage, and, if necessary, individual fragments of the local storage history are synchronized with the same storage on another computer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It contains basic elements that can be found in almost any README.md:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First level heading for title
Bolding Important Parts in the Description
Link to website with clear text
Second level heading for subparagraphs
Bulleted list to list benefits
Although Markdown is reasonably readable in its original form, it is often translated into HTML.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 post&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
